Contact

989156179233 (Mobile) hosseinakbari506@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ hosseinakbari506 (LinkedIn) ticnet.ir (Company) hosseinakbari506.ir (Personal)

Top Skills

PHP

HTML5 & CSS3

Search Engine Optimization (SEO)

Languages

English

Persian

Hossein Akbari

Front-End Developer

Iran

Summary

I'm a Front-End web developer, SEO expert and the founder at Ticnet. I try to increase my knowledge and expertise every day and also try to do the project in the best quality. I work hard to apply my core knowledge of Js combined with a keen interest in current and emerging technologies to make an effective solution.

Experience

Ticnet

Owner

June 2019 - Present (1 year)

Iran, Mashhad

Ticnet is a free, professional, easy-to-use website that lets you design your own website in a matter of minutes without the technical know-how.

Novinadmin

Website Management

September 2019 - January 2020 (5 months)

Iran, Mashhad

My main job at Novin Admin was managing several news and corporate websites. Content production and SEO were also another part of my activities.

Education

National Organization for Development of Exceptional Talents (Sampad)

High School, High School/Secondary Diplomas and Certificates · (2017 - 2020)